[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
There's a reason you're still alive.
What are you saying?
For 20 years, I prepared for this very moment.
How could you be so sure that this day would come?
That I'd still keep our promise?
Our plans.
I was slowly preparing this for your return.
Don't waste your pain.
Make it your reason to fight.
Let's help each other. While you seek justice,
I will help you live your life again.
If someone is making a move around Mikoy and Chiara,
we can't rule out
that they're connected to La Concordat.
We don't know yet. No assumptions.
We need facts.
Mario. Some information came in at the agency.
It's not verified yet.
So I can't give you the details.
Keep an eye on your surroundings for now.
I'll handle things here.
-Mario! -Mario!
Mario, there's a fire!
Come on, let's go!
Hurry up!
-Faster! -Sir Mario.
Where?
-Over there! -Hurry!
Let's get out!
-Bags. -Quick!
-What's the update? -Mar.
Looks like the portable fan overheated.
Good thing we noticed it right away,
so the fire didn't spread.
It was pretty close to our house, too.
My buzz is gone.
I got really scared, Mario.
Thank God no one got hurt, right?
Exactly.
Okay, Mar.
We'll double-check the area first.
Okay, okay. Thanks.
Come out!
Hurry.
Mario.
Good thing it was just a small fire.
I thought there was another Manananggal.
But this isn't an isolated incident.
Especially now that there's someone lurking around,
that vigilante you call a Manananggal.
But we've been through this before.
In Cebu.
Remember how it started small, then got worse over time?
But, Captain Pepe, maybe tomorrow,
you can start patrolling again.
Not because we're panicking.
We just want to make sure we're safe.
-Yes, Mario. -We're game!
Wait, one more thing.
As much as possible,
don't tell anyone about this. Not a soul.
Especially Chiara and Mikoy.
They already have enough on their plate.
We don't need to add to it.
-You heard what Mario said. -These two are such gossips.
Yes, sir. Yes, Mario.
Yes? You two gossips?
-No, sir. -We're just drunk.
Oh, gosh.
Here's your water bottle, sweetheart.
I didn't wake you up early
because I thought,
of course, my future wife needs her beauty rest.
We wouldn't want her turning into a beast, right?
My sweetheart is so sweet. He even got me
a tumbler.
You remind me of someone
I used to date
-in Hong Kong. -Huh?
Dasho.
You know, I know him too.
I know he's handsome and quite the catch,
that Dasho.
Yes, he's kind of like Mr. Suave.
Thank you, sweetheart,
for taking care of me and for everything.
There you go.
Why are you being so sweet today, sweetheart?
What's the occasion?
You want something again, don't you?
What could my sweetheart possibly want?
-You idiot! -Why?
I'm just kidding.
I was just thinking.
What if we don't go through with the wedding?
Dara.
Dara!
Look.
Sean looked like such an idiot. He was so drunk at the bridal shower.
Carlota, I was there. I saw it in person.
Were you there?
Yes. You're just so whipped.
You don't notice anything else except that Sianong.
Well,
if by whipped, you mean head over heels,
then yes.
I'm head over heels in love with him.
Anyway,
look at this. Here.
This is my favorite!
There! Look.
Why do you look like you didn't sleep?
I didn't.
Sean kept me up all night.
Wait, wait. What does TMI mean?
I don't want to talk about it.
That's not what it means.
No.
I mean, I have some intel.
I mean, we're still getting married.
It'll be simpler, more intimate.
Fewer…
Fewer what?
Fewer preparations.
Right?
It'll be cheaper, too.
Think about it.
Come here.
Look at me.
We're going through with the wedding.
We're having the church wedding,
we're having the reception,
and yes, we're doing our dance numbers, too. Okay?
I know you want everything to be simple,
but I also know that's not really the reason.
I know you're worried that your mom and dad won't be able to make it.
I'm worried about that too, sweetheart.
Of course, I'm sad that they won't be there, too.
Because I want them to see you walk down the aisle.
I want them to see your smile
as you walk toward the altar.
Right?
And of course, I want to hear your dad say,
just because they're not here
doesn't mean we shouldn't have a wedding.
If anything, I think we should go through with it even more.
Yes.
So that someday,
when we're finally reunited with them,
we can be proud that
we still made their dream come true, of a happy life for you.
Right?
And one more thing, sweetheart.
So many people helped us get this far.
This wedding
isn't just a celebration for the two of us.
It's also our way of saying thank you
to everyone who loved us and helped us along the way.
Oh, and sweetheart,
we've already paid our suppliers so much.
What a waste!
Oh my!
I thought you were being serious.
I am serious, sweetheart.
I'm just being practical, right?
But wait.
Why?
Did you get a last-minute love confession?
Is someone trying to steal you away?
Hey! If there is, let them come out.
-What? -Sweetheart.
They can all keep quiet forever.
You guys are something else.
Did you hear about what happened to Ma'am's husband?
The one who used to be here?
The bald guy, Viktor Valtrovi?
Yes. Apparently, he got badly beaten up.
They even had to take him to the clinic last night.
What happened? Was there a riot?
It's still unclear.
All they said was he could barely stand.
I think we made the wrong call letting him stay here.
HQ is going to come after us for this.
General Norberto might find out.
Let's go.
Word is Viktor underwent a medical exam.
Why?
Because of the severity of his injuries.
Injuries?
How is he?
It's still unclear.
There's no conclusive report yet.
We still don't know if there was a fight or if he committed some violation inside.
Hold on.
Carlota, why do you seem so concerned about Viktor?
Wasn't he the one who wanted to have you killed?
Yes.
But that doesn't mean we both have to be bad people.
Besides,
But
I feel even worse for Chiara.
You're worried about Chiara too?
I thought you two weren't on good terms.
That was before.
But she's different now.
And she's no longer the hot-headed assassin she used to be.
Carlota, do you have a fever?
You're worried about two people who wanted to kill you?
Maybe we can talk to General Norberto?
There's an update.
No special permit.
Viktor and Donabel won't be able to attend the wedding.
Chiara, Mikoy, dinner's ready!
Come out already!
-Hey, Vicky, I have a question for you. -Go ahead.
Are Italian men sweet?
-At first. -But?
Once football comes into the picture,
you won't have a husband anymore.
Well, I never married an Italian.
I just heard those stories
from my friends and colleagues who married Italians.
That's where I heard them.
Okay, one more question.
If you had to choose,
Depends.
On what?
On who knows how to wash the dishes.
Good answer! You know my Mario?
I was the one who taught him. Yes.
So, Mikoy,
do you know how to wash the dishes?
Oh, really! Me? Of course I do!
I know how to wash the dishes,
iron, sweep, and do the laundry.
I even know how to bake. I can do a somersault and shake my hips.
Wow! Well, well, well.
My girl really is lucky to have you!
Oh, very lucky, Mama Vicky.
I've truly been blessed with him.
You two became such close friends so quickly!
Tell me about it!
You know, I feel like
we've been friends for so long already.
Right? And because of that,
I have an idea, kids.
Because, your Ninang Mylene won't be able to make it to your wedding
because of a family emergency…
It's such a shame, yes, but I guess it's a blessing in disguise.
Why?
Because Vicky has agreed to be your wedding godmother.
Yes!
-Really? -Yes!
Thank you so much!
Mommy Vicky.
I'm just a little embarrassed because
we don't really know each other that well yet.
For now.
Don't worry. We'll get to know each other better.
I still have plenty of time to keep an eye on you
and see if you're really perfect for my girl.
Yes, ma'am.
Behave yourself, Mikoy.
Let's eat.
This smells good.
So sweet!
I thought you were the bride.
Why are you sneaking away?
I am the bride,
not a hostage.
How are they?
Well…
Last I heard,
your mom is still as stubborn as ever,
and your dad is even more stubborn.
It's scarier when Dad is nice.
It's even scarier when you're nice to me.
Well, there's been a little character development.
The former hot-headed brat I knew
is now a slightly less hot-headed country girl.
Well, it's easier to breathe in the fresh air here.
And it's refreshing to have clean and clear life intentions.
What?
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
I just hope…
Let's hope Viktor and Donabel can make it.
Besides,
it would be a shame if they couldn't make it, right?
You're their only daughter, after all.
It would be perfect if they could make it.
You know what?
Let's manifest it.
Wait a minute.
I thought our relationship was leveling up.
Why am I still a Chihuahua?
Come on. Let's go inside.
They're waiting for you.
Hey, what are you doing?
You look like you're deep in thought.
You've been stirring that coffee for three hours.
Cocoy.
What if we help Viktor?
How do we help Viktor?
We break him out.
What?
It will be quick.
We'll just get him out,
then bring him back after the wedding.
Like we're just borrowing him.
Come on, Carlota.
Viktor is a person, not something that you can return after borrowing.
Then,
Look.
Do you really think that if Viktor escapes,
he'll come back?
I'm just worried.
Something's wrong.
But I have a crush on you.
I have a crush on you too.
So we're crushiecakes now?
Is it still replaying in your head?
Alex.
Is it that obvious?
Very.
Can't we just erase whatever happened that night?
We can't. It's already written.
You know, Alex, you know how
I confessed while I was drunk,
and then we even got married?
Doesn't that make me seem so easy?
It's embarrassing.
Now that you've finally said how you really feel,
I mean, you're free now.
You've already won.
Not because you'll end up together.
You've won because
you're no longer lying about how you really feel.
And you don't have anything to hide anymore.
That's true.
It's just really hard to repress your feelings.
You know, it's kind of constipating?
Isn't that true?
Oh, Sofie.
Right, Alex?
Do you get what I mean?
Well, if those hidden feelings are stressing you out,
then yes,
it can affect your gut health.
But if you both feel the same way,
then that's good.
I think you'll be fine.
You even got married, right?
But wasn't he drunk too?
Well, if he wasn't,
at least you're free to move forward now.
You're right.
I've said what I needed to say.
Now, it's up to him.
Chiara.
Are you okay?
Yes, Mom. I'm okay.
I thought you were upset because I made Vicky your wedding godmother.
No, Mom.
I was just surprised, but of course, I'm happy because
I never thought Mama Yaya and I would see each other again.
You two really clicked so quickly, the two of you.
I know, right?
You know, it's like because we've become such good friends,
she feels like the sister I never had.
You have a missing sister?
No, hello.
It just feels that way.
Yes.
You know, I really hope they allow your mom to come here.
Then the three of us will be complete.
Rosario, Rosenda, and Rosemarie.
Who are they?
Why, the three Claudines!
Maybe you weren't even born back then!
Wait a minute.
What do you mean?
We'll just be the Powerpuff Girls. I'm Bubbles.
Perfect. Mama Yaya and I both love Blossom.
Then Donabel can be Buttercup.
She's the hothead, after all.
Doesn't that fit?
I hope they get approved.
Oh, dear.
If that happens,
poor Mario.
We'll all be bossing him around at the same time.
Auntie Mercy, maybe we can get
a future-husband discount here!
There you go!
A discount! Perfect timing. I'm vlogging her!
Come on.
-Perfect timing. He's vlogging. -You're something else, Mikoy.
Fine, just add these two pieces.
-Yes! -Yes!
Thank you, Mommy Mercy!
Thank you!
-There you go. Thank you! -Thank you!
You're really good at this, Mikoy!
Of course!
Bro.
Thank you.
For what?
For Mom.
I didn't expect you guys to accept her like that.
Why wouldn't we?
You're important to us.
So naturally, she's important to us too.
Really?
Because, Bro,
she just showed up out of nowhere, and then
she's already the godmother.
I was surprised too.
But look at her and Mom Tess, right?
They act like they've been friends forever!
And it's actually nice that she was Chiara's nanny.
When you think about it,
doesn't that mean you and Chiara are practically siblings now?
Right?
Exactly.
And Chiara seems happy about it, right?
Of course!
Of course, and so am I.
-I'm over the moon that my bride is happy. -Nice.
Hey!
-Where are you from? -I'm getting late.
Where are you from?
Not far.
-All right. -Just on the corner of the street.
-Okay, buddy, head on in. -Where is this located?
Is this even Team Groom anymore?
It's starting to look like a security agency.
Let me take a look first.
-How do you know him? -He's my brother.
Okay, brother-in-law.
-Sir. -Bro.
-I go here frequently. -Could there be a reason for this?
Wait, where are you heading? Stop.
-What is that? -Let me take a look.
Don't they seem a little too serious?
-Keep going straight. -I need to hurry.
Wait, Captain Pepe, Mario.
What is this for?
They weren't like this before.
I totally knew that.
Those moves are full of doubts.
I know, because I used to be like that!
Hang on. We have to take a selfie.
We will make them jealous. We're all so pretty today.
See? I'm going to send this to him.
Look, Tess sent a groupie.
We can't lose. Mikoy!
Carlota?
What are you doing here?
Did Senator Quintin send you?
If he's the one who sent me,
I wouldn't give you a tissue. Donabel,
Let's go.